Duke Padmore

FRONT END DEVELOPER JAVASCRIPT - REACT

AVAILABLE FROM JANUARY 2023

"Thanks to my adaptability, my training, my proficiency in both French & English, as well as my endless desire to learn, I was able to successfully take up new challenges in various fields. I have now transitioned to a career in web development, which I have always been passionate about, and I look forward to an opportunity to discuss the skills and experience that I can bring to your organization."

CONTACT

dukepadmore@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/dukepadmore

LANGUAGES

French: native English: C2 Spanish: B2 Japanese: A1

SOFT SKILLS

Analytical mind
Problem solver
Curiosity
Team work
Detail-oriented
Creativity
Sense of urgency
Autonomy & adaptability
Client-oriented

INTERESTS

New technologies
Foreign languages (currently learning Japanese)
Basketball: 15+ years
Photography
Piano

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- <u>Front-end:</u> HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, ReactJS, Responsive design, AJAX, Redux, Sass, Tailwind CSS
- <u>Back-end:</u> Node.Js, Express, Sequelize, API REST, SQL, NoSQL, PostgreSQL
- Other tools & concepts: Git, GitHub, Agile methodology,
 OOP

EDUCATION

FULLSTACK JAVASCRIPT WEB DEVELOPMENT TRAINING

O'Clock | March 2022 - Sep. 2022

<u>Curriculum key features:</u>

- Daily individual programming challenges after every training day
- Weekly pair-programming sessions
- 1-month final project : development of a project from design to deployment, as a team and in real-life conditions
- ReactJS specialization

MASTER'S DEGREE - PURCHASING & INNOVATION MANAGEMENT

Kedge Business School | 2018

BACHELOR'S DEGREE - FOREIGN LANGUAGES

Paris-Nanterre University | 2011

EXPERIENCE

GEFCO

Country Buyer | 2019 - 2022 Global Indirect Buyer | 2018 - 2019

NIKE INC.

Assistant Store Manager | 2017 - 2018 Team Leader | 2016 - 2017 Sales Associate | 2014 - 2016